hostelz.com 2015-10-07

# Privacy Policy - Hostelz.com

## Cookies

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

## Registration

Registration is not required to use the site, but some special services, such as posting comments or submitting reviews or making a booking, require a valid email address. We will not add you to any mailing lists and we don't send out any emails other than an initial email to confirm your email address.

## Sharing of Information

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third party booking systems who are handling your booking request, or accommodations where you have made a booking. Bookings through Hostelz.com are processed by third party booking sites. These companies have their own privacy policies which may differ from that of Hostelz.com, but we only work with companies that value your privacy and have agreed to keep your information confidential. Their policies, terms, and conditions may be viewed from the booking form page when you submit a booking. We seek to protect the integrity of our users and welcome any feedback about these sites. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.

## How we protect your information

All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into the payment gateway provider's database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

## California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent except as necessary according to the terms of this privacy policy.

## Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act). We do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products, and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

## Your Consent

By using our site you consent to our privacy policy.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy we will post those changes on this page. 

Copyright © 2015 Hostelz.com
